Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Mexico File, 1956-1961
  - Correspondence, 1957-1961
    - G-M
      - Gallardo Moreno, Juan, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 1)
      - Gallego, Augusto M., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 2)
      - Gallegos Nunez, Alicia de, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 3)
      - Gamba, Enrique, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 4)
      - Gambrell, Guy, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 5)
      - Gamio, Manuel, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 51: 6)
      - Gammons, Earl H., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 51: 7)
      - Gandara, Cesar A., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 8)
      - Gangu, J. K., 1957 (Box-folder 51: 9)
      - Gannett, James A., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 10)
      - Ganus, James W., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 11)
      - Garcia, Adolfo, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 12)
      - Garcia, Francisco E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 13)
      - Garcia, Luis, Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 14)
      - Garcia Battle, Leobardo, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 15)
      - Garcia Borras, Jose, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 16)
      - Garcia Cabral, Ernesto, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 17)
      - Garcia Gonzalez, Alfonso, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 18)
      - Garcia la Sienra, Ramon, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 19)
      - Garcia Montero, Francisco, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 20)
      - Garcia Quevedo, Antonio, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 21)
      - Garcia Ruiz, Antonio, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 22)
      - Garcia Silva, Francisco, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 23)
      - Garcia T., Guillermina, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 24)
      - Garcia Valseca, Jose, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 25)
      - Garcia Villalobos, Ricardo, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 26)
      - Gardiner, George B., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 27)
      - Gardiner, Nona L., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 28)
      - Gardner, George P., Jr., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 51: 29)
      - Gardner, John W., 1958 (Box-folder 51: 30)
      - Gardner, Laurence F., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 31)
      - Gardner, Ledyard D., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 32)
      - Garduno, Julio J., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 33)
      - Garibi Rivera, Joseph, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 51: 34)
      - Garland, Charles H., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 35)
      - Garlock, Lorena A., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 36)
      - Garner, John N., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 37)
      - Garnett, Gwynn, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 38)
      - Garran, Peter, undated (Box-folder 51: 39)
      - Garrett, Glenn E., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 40)
      - Garside, Mrs. William Preston, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 41)
      - Garza Ruiz, Antonio, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 42)
      - Garza Sanchez, Eduardo, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 43)
      - Gassaway, Gerrish, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 44)
      - Gates, Thomas S., Jr., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 45)
      - Gaudet, William G., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 51: 46)
      - Gauss, Blane E., 1958 (Box-folder 51: 47)
      - Gaxiola Andrade, Radames, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 48)
      - Gay, Edward R., 1957 (Box-folder 51: 49)
      - Geach, Robert, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 50)
      - Geiger, H. J., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 51)
      - Genova, Mario H. di, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 52)
      - George, David R., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 53)
      - Gerdes, Mauricio, 1957 (Box-folder 51: 54)
      - Gerrity, T. P., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 55)
      - Gershenson, Robert S., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 51: 56)
      - Giampiccolo, Lucy, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 57)
      - Gibbins, George, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 58)
      - Gibbons, Eliot, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 59)
      - Gil Preciado, Juan, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 60)
      - Gildred, Theodore, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 61)
      - Giles, Harland, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 62)
      - Gillentine, Jimmy, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 63)
      - Gilsey, Peter Ladd, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 64)
      - Glawe, Benoid E., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 65)
      - Gleason, Francis J., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 66)
      - Gleason, H. E., 1958 (Box-folder 51: 67)
      - Gleason, James P., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 68)
      - Glenn, Charles Leslie, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 69)
      - Glenn, John B., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 51: 70)
      - Glode, John B., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 71)
      - Glover, Irene Buchanan de, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 72)
      - Gold, Jeanne, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 73)
      - Goldthwaite, Robert, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 74)
      - Gollong, Paul B. W., 1958 (Box-folder 51: 75)
      - Gomez, Barbara B. de, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 76)
      - Gomez, Marte R., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 77)
      - Gomez, Rodrigo, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 78)
      - Gomez C., Manuel, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 79)
      - Gomez Haro, Octavio, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 80)
      - Gomez Huerta, Jose, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 81)
      - Gomez Maqueo, Roberto, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 82)
      - Gomez Morin, Manuel, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 83)
      - Gomez Sada, Napoleon, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 84)
      - Gonzalez, Carlos, 1957 (Box-folder 51: 85)
      - Gonzalez, Cesar, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 51: 86)
      - Gonzalez, Edmundo, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 51: 87)
      - Gonzalez, Ernesto, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 88)
      - Gonzalez, Fidel L., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 51: 89)
      - Gonzalez, Hector R., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 90)
      - Gonzalez, J. Natalicio, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 91)
      - Gonzalez, Lee, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 92)
      - Gonzalez A., Jose, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 93)
      - Gonzalez Blanco, J. P., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 94)
      - Gonzalez Castro, Elias, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 95)
      - Gonzalez Diaz Lombardo, Francisco, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 96)
      - Gonzalez Gollaz, Ignacio, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 97)
      - Gonzalez Guevara, Hector, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 98)
      - Gonzalez M., Mario, 1959 (Box-folder 51: 99)
      - Gonzalez Moreno, Enrique, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 100)
      - Gonzalez Rivas, Ignacio B., 1959 (Box-folder 51: 101)
      - Gonzalez V. de Munoz, Maria Cristina, 1960 (Box-folder 51: 102)
      - Gooden, Reginald Heber, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 103)
      - Goodhue, L. Cushing, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 104)
      - Goodrich, Burnell N., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 51: 105)
      - Goodrich, Emmette K., Jr., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 51: 106)
      - Goodrich, George G., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 51: 107)
      - Goodrich, Paul W., 1960 (Box-folder 51: 108)
      - Goodspeed, H. Kent, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 52: 1)
      - Goodwin, Frances, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 2)
      - Gordon, Darley Fuller, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 3)
      - Gordon, Mary Agnes, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 4)
      - Gordon, Mrs. Thomas S., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 5)
      - Goroste, Pedro, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 6)
      - Gorostiza, Celestino, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 52: 7)
      - Gorostiza, Jose, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 52: 8)
      - Gorraez, Juan C., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 9)
      - Gosden, Freeman F., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 10)
      - Gott, Philip P., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 52: 11)
      - Gould, Ann, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 12)
      - Gould, Charles L., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 13)
      - Gould, Florence M., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 14)
      - Gould, Franklin P., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 15)
      - Gowen, Franklin C., 1958 (Box-folder 52: 16)
      - Goyen, John W., Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 17)
      - Goyeneche, Rafael C., 1958 (Box-folder 52: 18)
      - Grace, J. Peter, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 19)
      - Graham, Billy, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 20)
      - Graham, Judd, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 21)
      - Graham, William L., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 22)
      - Grambach, Paul V., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 23)
      - Grand, Stanley I., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 52: 24)
      - Grant, Nick, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 52: 25)
      - Gray, A. D., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 26)
      - Gray, Cecil W., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 52: 27)
      - Gray, George O., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 28)
      - Gray, William P., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 29)
      - Gray, William R., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 30)
      - Grebe, Barbara, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 31)
      - Green, Clinton H., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 32)
      - Green, Timothy, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 52: 33)
      - Green, Walter L., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 34)
      - Greene, Abe J., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 35)
      - Greene, Charles H., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 36)
      - Greene, Francis T., 1957 (Box-folder 52: 37)
      - Greene, Frank T., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 38)
      - Greene, Joseph N., Jr., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 52: 39)
      - Greenblatt, Irving, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 40)
      - Grefe, Donald C., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 41)
      - Gregg, Hugh, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 52: 42)
      - Grenas Gooding, Luis, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 43)
      - Griffith, J. Neal, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 44)
      - Grinnell, George H., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 45)
      - Griswold, Erwin N., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 46)
      - Groome, David R., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 52: 47)
      - Gross, Robert E., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 48)
      - Grossman, Burton E., 1957 (Box-folder 52: 49)
      - Gruening, Ernest, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 50)
      - Gruenther, Homer H., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 52: 51)
      - Guadalajara. Universidad Autonoma, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 52)
      - Guajardo, Apolonio, 1957 (Box-folder 52: 53)
      - Guajardo Suarez, Roberto, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 54)
      - Guardia, Fernando de la, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 55)
      - Guardia H., Enrique de la, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 56)
      - Guerra Fernandez, Armando, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 57)
      - Guerrero Almada, Gonzalo, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 58)
      - Guerrero Guajardo, Anacleto, 1957 (Box-folder 52: 59)
      - Guest, Winston, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 60)
      - Guevara, Antonio, 1957 (Box-folder 52: 61)
      - Guider, John W., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 62)
      - Guilbert, Robert M., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 63)
      - Guill, Ben H., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 52: 64)
      - Guillen Caamano, Manuel, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 65)
      - Guisa Venegas, Hector, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 66)
      - Guiscafre-Arrillaga, Jaime, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 67)
      - Guizar, Nina, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 68)
      - Gullette, Wilmer, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 69)
      - Gurza, Alejandro, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 70)
      - Gurza, Mrs. Tomas, 1957 (Box-folder 52: 71)
      - Gustafson, Andy, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 72)
      - Guth, Jenny-Lynn, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 73)
      - Gutierrez, Eulalio, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 74)
      - Gutierrez, Jose G., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 52: 75)
      - Gutierrez Mora, Jose Manuel, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 76)
      - Gutierrez Prieto, Antonio, 1957 (Box-folder 52: 77)
      - Gutierrez Roldan, Pascual, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 78)
      - Guylay, L. Richard, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 79)
      - Guzman, Martin Lius, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 80)
      - Guzman, Plutarco, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 81)
      - Guzman Neyra, Alfonso, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 82)
      - Guzman Orozco, Renaldo, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 83)
      - Guzman Valdes, Ramon, 1958 (Box-folder 52: 84)
      - Habberton, John, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 85)
      - Hachten, John E., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 86)
      - Hackney, G. Edgar, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 52: 87)
      - Hadley, James Edgar, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 88)
      - Hagan, Mrs. Frank, 1959 (Box-folder 52: 89)
      - Hagerman, Donald C., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 52: 90)
      - Hagerty, James C., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 52: 91)
      - Haines, Johnson A., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 52: 92)
      - Hajen, Bernardo, 1960 (Box-folder 52: 93)
      - Hall, Leonard W., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 94)
      - Hall, Richard R., 1960 (Box-folder 52: 95)
      - Hallman, William H., 1959 (Box-folder 52: 96)
      - Halpenny, Leonard C., 1958 (Box-folder 52: 97)
      - Hamer, Walter M., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 1)
      - Hamilton, Wesley D., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 2)
      - Hammarskjold, Dag, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 3)
      - Hammonds, Oliver W., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 4)
      - Hancock, Robert A., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 5)
      - Hands, H. W., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 6)
      - Hanes, John W., Jr., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 7)
      - Hanna, Richard T., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 8)
      - Hannifin, Jerry, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 53: 9)
      - Hanson, Hjalmar F., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 10)
      - Hanson, Simon, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 11)
      - Harden, J. E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 53: 12)
      - Hardison, Jimmy, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 13)
      - Hardy, Royce A., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 14)
      - Harkness, Albert, Jr., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 15)
      - Harlow, Bryce N., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 16)
      - Harrell, Samuel R., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 17)
      - Harrington, Julian F., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 53: 18)
      - Harris, Arthur, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 19)
      - Harris, J. B., 1961 (Box-folder 53: 20)
      - Harris, Nancy, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 21)
      - Harris, Richard C., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 53: 22)
      - Harris, Roger, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 23)
      - Harris, Virginia Littlejohn, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 24)
      - Harrison, Roberta, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 25)
      - Harrover, William F., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 53: 26)
      - Harshberger, Marvin L., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 27)
      - Harshman, Samuel C., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 53: 28)
      - Harte, Edward H., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 29)
      - Hartmann, Robert T., 1957 (Box-folder 53: 30)
      - Harvard University, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 31)
      - Harvey, F. Barton, Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 32)
      - Harvey, John F., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 53: 33)
      - Harwood, Herbert H., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 34)
      - Hasenkamp, Caroline M., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 35)
      - Hastings, Earl F., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 36)
      - Hatt, Mrs. Robert T., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 37)
      - Haubrich, Wilson R., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 38)
      - Hauge, Gabriel, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 39)
      - Haughton, Daniel J., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 40)
      - Havers, John L., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 41)
      - Haverty, James, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 42)
      - Hayden, John C., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 43)
      - Hazlett, Thomas J., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 44)
      - Hazzard, Michael S., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 45)
      - Heacock, Jack, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 46)
      - Head, Hayden W., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 47)
      - Head, Martin F., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 48)
      - Heald, L. Franklin, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 49)
      - Heald, Walter, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 50)
      - Healey, H. Max, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 51)
      - Healy, George W., Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 52)
      - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 53)
      - Heaton, C. R., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 54)
      - Hebbard, Sterling, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 55)
      - Hebdon, Horace T., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 56)
      - Hector, Louis J., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 57)
      - Hedlund, Richard A., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 58)
      - Hefter, J., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 59)
      - Heimark, Jacob V., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 60)
      - Heising, Dewey R., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 53: 61)
      - Helguera, Leon, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 62)
      - Hellyer, David, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 53: 63)
      - Henderson, Forrest E., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 53: 64)
      - Henle, Ray, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 65)
      - Henry, Bill, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 66)
      - Henshel, Walter M., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 67)
      - Herd, Harold H., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 68)
      - Hernandez, Antonio, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 69)
      - Hernandez, Ernesto, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 70)
      - Hernandez, Hilario, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 71)
      - Hernandez, Luis Lauro, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 72)
      - Hernandez Alvarez, Everardo, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 73)
      - Hernandez Chacon, Pedro, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 74)
      - Hernandez Delgado, Jose, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 75)
      - Hernandez Ibarra, Jorge, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 76)
      - Hernandez Partida, Leopoldo, 1957 (Box-folder 53: 77)
      - Hernandez Serrano, Leopoldo, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 78)
      - Hernandez Soto, Narciso, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 53: 79)
      - Herrera de la Fuente, Luis, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 80)
      - Herrera Rossi, Jose, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 53: 81)
      - Herrick, Dwight B., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 82)
      - Herrick, Elinore Morehouse, 1959 (Box-folder 53: 83)
      - Herron, Bill, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 84)
      - Hershberg, Abraham M., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 85)
      - Hershcopf, Samuel, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 86)
      - Hess, Jerome S., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 87)
      - Hess, Walter, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 88)
      - Hessler, William H., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 89)
      - Hestand, Jo, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 90)
      - Hester, W. R., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 91)
      - Hewatt, W. A., 1958 (Box-folder 53: 92)
      - Hickey, Frank E., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 53: 93)
      - Hickey, William M., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 53: 94)
      - Hickingbotham, Joseph C., Jr., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 53: 95)
      - Hicks, C. D., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 53: 96)
      - Hicks, Cordell, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 53: 97)
      - Hicks, Orton H., 1960 (Box-folder 53: 98)
      - Hidalgo, Edward, 1958 (Box-folder 53: 99)
      - Hiermeier, Virgil H., 1957 (Box-folder 53: 100)
      - Higgins, Lawrence, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 1)
      - Higgins, Marguerite, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 2)
      - Higginson, Henry L., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 3)
      - High, Robert King, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 4)
      - Highmark, Bob, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 5)
      - Hightower, Robert, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 6)
      - Hill, Ed, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 7)
      - Hill, Karl A., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 54: 8)
      - Hill, Sam B., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 9)
      - Hill, Tina M., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 10)
      - Hillman, Alex L., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 11)
      - Hilton, Ronald, 1957 (Box-folder 54: 12)
      - Hinojosa, Libia Z. de, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 13)
      - Hirschfeld, Julio V., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 14)
      - Hirschfeld, Mary, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 15)
      - Hixson, Howard Dale, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 54: 16)
      - Ho, Feng-shan, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 17)
      - Hodgson, Morton S., Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 18)
      - Hoerner, R. N., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 54: 19)
      - Hoerster, Sam A., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 20)
      - Hoffman, Paul G., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 21)
      - Hogan, B. W., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 22)
      - Hogg, Jacqueline, 1957 (Box-folder 54: 23)
      - Hogg, V. E., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 24)
      - Hoghland, John S., II, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 54: 25)
      - Hohenberg, A. E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 54: 26)
      - Holcomb, Luther, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 27)
      - Holden, Maurice C., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 28)
      - Holguin Reza, Domingo, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 29)
      - Holland, Henry F., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 54: 30)
      - Holland, Leslie T., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 31)
      - Hollar, Philip A., 1957 (Box-folder 54: 32)
      - Holley, Myle J., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 33)
      - Holliday, W. J., Jr., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 34)
      - Hollister, John B., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 35)
      - Holman, Eugene, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 36)
      - Holmes, Frank J., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 37)
      - Holmes, Julius C., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 38)
      - Holmes, Robert D., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 39)
      - Holt, Barbara Hill, undated (Box-folder 54: 40)
      - Holzhauer, Harry William, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 41)
      - Hooper, Sidney L., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 42)
      - Hoover, Herbert, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 43)
      - Hoover, Herbert, Jr., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 44)
      - Hoover, Howard, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 54: 45)
      - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 46)
      - Hopkins, Charles S., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 47)
      - Hopkins, Robert S., Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 48)
      - Hopper, Robert L., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 49)
      - Hopps, Byron, 1957 (Box-folder 54: 50)
      - Horan, Frank, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 51)
      - Horcasitas, Andres, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 52)
      - Horn, Adolf B., Jr., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 54: 53)
      - Horn, Charles W., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 54)
      - Hosley, Diana, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 55)
      - Hotaling, N. L., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 56)
      - Hotchkis, Preston, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 57)
      - Houghton, Amory, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 54: 58)
      - House, Howard P., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 59)
      - Houston, W. V., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 60)
      - Hoving, John, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 61)
      - Howard, David, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 62)
      - Howe, John, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 63)
      - Howell, Gillie C., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 64)
      - Hoxter, Curtis J., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 65)
      - Hubbard, Miriam, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 66)
      - Huber, Ferdinand V., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 67)
      - Hubscher, Paul, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 68)
      - Hudson, E. J., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 69)
      - Huguenot Society of America, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 70)
      - Hulse, Gilbert Rodwell, 1957 (Box-folder 54: 71)
      - Humphreys, J. W., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 54: 72)
      - Humphreys, Robert, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 73)
      - Hunsaker, Lee M., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 54: 74)
      - Hunt, Lewis W., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 54: 75)
      - Hunter, David R., 1957 (Box-folder 54: 76)
      - Hurley, Patrick J., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 54: 77)
      - Hurley, Roy T., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 78)
      - Hurtado, Gloria, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 79)
      - Huston, Harris H., 1958 (Box-folder 54: 80)
      - Huston, Herbert, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 81)
      - Huthsteiner, R. E., 1959 (Box-folder 54: 82)
      - Hyams, Joe, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 83)
      - Hyde, J. F. C., Jr., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 54: 84)
      - Hyman, Joseph B., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 54: 85)
      - Ibanez Parkman, Roberto, 1958 (Box-folder 54: 86)
      - Ibanez Zaldivar, Abel, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 87)
      - Ibarguen, Carlos, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 88)
      - Iles, Roy, 1960 (Box-folder 54: 89)
      - Illescas Frisbie, Rafael, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 90)
      - Imhof, Fred, 1959 (Box-folder 54: 91)
      - Imle, Ernest P., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 54: 92)
      - Infante, Jose, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 1)
      - Innes, Diego, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 2)
      - International Christian Leadership, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 55: 3)
      - International Good Neighbor Council, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 4)
      - Inurreta, Marcelino, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 5)
      - Irwin, Clayton, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 55: 6)
      - Ischursin, Diana, 1960 (Box-folder 55: 7)
      - Iturriaga Villegas, Enrique, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 8)
      - Izaguirre, Antonino B., 1960 (Box-folder 55: 9)
      - Izaguirre Bali, Lauro, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 10)
      - Izquierdo Albinana, Francisco, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 55: 11)
      - Jack, Ronald, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 12)
      - Jacob, C. W., 1958 (Box-folder 55: 13)
      - Jacobs, Joseph E., 1959 (Box-folder 55: 14)
      - Jacobsen, Jake, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 55: 15)
      - Jacobson, M., 1957 (Box-folder 55: 16)
      - Jafke, Orville W., 1959 (Box-folder 55: 17)
      - Jagou, Charles C., 1958 (Box-folder 55: 18)
      - Jahn, Richard P., 1960 (Box-folder 55: 19)
      - Jalil, C. J., 1957 (Box-folder 55: 20)
      - James, Daniel, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 55: 21)
      - Janville, Jan, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 22)
      - Jaquet, Harold H., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 55: 23)
      - Jarrett, Edward, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 24)
      - Jarvis, Ellis A., 1960 (Box-folder 55: 25)
      - Jasper, Susie, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 26)
      - Jenkins, Walter, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 55: 27)
      - Jenney, Robert M., 1958 (Box-folder 55: 28)
      - Jensen, Laurel, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 29)
      - Jergins, Allen A., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 55: 30)
      - Jessup, John K., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 55: 31)
      - Jimenez, Antonio Vera, 1959 (Box-folder 55: 32)
      - Jimenez C., Rafael, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 33)
      - Jimenez M., Federico G., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 55: 34)
      - Jimenez Rueda, Julio, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 35)
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1960 (Box-folder 55: 36)
      - Johnson, Mrs. Emery C., 1958 (Box-folder 55: 37)
      - Johnson, Frances Ann, 1960 (Box-folder 55: 38)
      - Johnson, Olof, 1960 (Box-folder 55: 39)
      - Johnson, U. Alexis, 1960 (Box-folder 55: 40)
      - Johnston, Eric, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 55: 41)
      - Johnston, Glenn, 1960 (Box-folder 55: 42)
      - Johnston, James D., 1960 (Box-folder 55: 43)
      - Johnston, Victor A., 1959 (Box-folder 55: 44)